[INTRO] I told you to refrain from UP when changing edges.
[INTRO] Unweighting, that is, losing weight...
[INTRO] Constant effort is needed to make this stable.
[INTRO] When they do DOWN, they just sit there for a short time.
[INTRO] You don't have to put a hand on the slopes first.
[INTRO] If this happens, you'll lose your butt...
This is a season lesson video.
I strongly recommend you to watch the previous videos and practice them in order.
If you do not practice with equipment properly set or not following previous steps,
you may have no effect.
Hello, I'm Seungwon Kim.
I came here with a season lesson after long time.
I think it's the sixth lesson today.
Until this lesson, you learned BBP posture, basic carving, angulation, and angulation in DOWN position.
When you're doing angulation in the low BBP position, I told you to refrain from using UP when you're doing edge change.
The reason is that during the process of UP and DOWN, the pelvis is often loosened, so I told you to refrain UP movement before changing the edge.
So, you probably felt discomfort during the change process.
I'm trying not to do UP as much as I can.
Unweighting, so we need to reduce the press on the deck and switch the edges, but there was no unweighting action,
so the edge change process must have been uncomfortable.
This time, we're going to mix up Up&Down.
And I think you did well with the previous steps,
so, I think you're a little closer to the slope if you're here by this lesson.
Now, We're going to put a hand on the slope with Up&Down today.
- How to change the edge -
There are two main ways to change the edge.
It's up-unweight and down-unweight.
Of course, there's a way to mix up-unweight and down-unweight called cross-through, but let's not discuss that.
It is usually divided into up-unweight and down-unweight.
Because up-unweight is technically easier,
so, it's good for beginners to try because they've been used to up-unweight since they started beginner turn and sliding turn.
So, we're going to do up-unweight this time.
I think it would be good to understand the difference between up-unweight and down-unweight before we do up-unweight.
Let me explain the pros and cons.
Up-unweight is easy to do, as I mentioned earlier.
So, people are used to doing edge-changing by the up-unweighting.
It's quite easy to do and intuitive.
Second, it's fairly stable.
The word "stable" doesn't mean anything else, but it's about edge grips.
In the case of up-unweight, we do "edging" accurately from the neutral section,
As the edge slowly tilts, it can make accurate contact and edging deep into slope,
and it's long enough to get edge grip, you can make more stable turn.
Third, it's good to ride while maintaining speed on the beginner's slope.
You can even ride accelerating using an up-unweight turn.
So, it is more advantageous to ride on beginner slopes or turn to accelerate.
Fourth, it consumes relatively less energy.
It's physically advantageous.
Lastly, the fifth one is subjective.
In case of up-unweight, it seems to ride quite comfortably compared to down-unweighted.
If you take a leisure ride up-unweight turn on the expert slopes,
you might seem to ride better.
-Down-unweight advantages-
In case of down-unweight turn, the edge change speed will be the fastest turn.
Therefore, it is good to slow down again.
It means that as soon as you do edge switching, you enter the position with high angle edge,
so it's pressurized throughout the turn, so it's good to control the speed.
That's why it's an advantageous edge change method worth riding on a expert slope.
Also, down-unweight turn will have the advantage of looking very dynamic visually.
So what's the downside?
Up-unweight is significantly larger in turn radius because edge change speed is a little slower than down-unweight.
So it can be a little difficult to ride on a narrow slope.
Also, since it's a turn that accelerates a lot,
Also, since it's a turn that accelerates a lot, there may be a disadvantage that it's difficult to ride on the expert slope.
On the other hand, the disadvantage of down-unweight is difficult to use for now.
It's a very difficult edge change method.
And I think it's a turn that takes more energy than up-unweight.
And finally, down-unweight, as I said earlier,
because of the difficulty level, edge switching is relatively disturbing.
After edge switching, you have to contact edge with very high edge angle,
so you can enter more unstable,
and you need to make constant efforts to change it to stable.
- Up-and-weight ground demonstration-
Now, I'll show you the UP and DOWN posture on the ground.
In case of UP, I told you that there are various heights in BBP posture,
including high BBP posture, medium BBP, and low BBP posture.
You don't have to do a full up height here.
You can do it according to your preference.
In other words, make sure you can do enough unweighting, but you don't have to do a full-up.
If I make a turn at this height,
I think I'll do a little up to this height when I do the UP.
It's about medium BBP. I think I'd do that much.
And when you do DOWN, you make a low position,
the important thing at that time, make sure to hold your pelvis on the neutral section so that it will never be loosed.
And the most important thing is that you shouldn't rush into DOWN.
when a lot of beginners went up and down,
they just sit down in a hurry.
If it's a certain timing, just sit in a trice.
I don't think there's any timing for DOWN.
I think if you started edge-changing, you'd slowly go down,
then the completion time is around fallline at the earliest.
Namely, you should think that you'll continue to doing DOWN until 3 or 9 PM.
But for beginners, they might not finish it until 3 o'clock,
DOWN might continue until 4 or 5 o'clock.
when you are beginner, you should do the DOWN until about 4 o'clock.
the If you get used to it later, until about 3 o'clock... If it's earlier, maybe 2:00 or 2:30...
you'll be able to complete the DOWN in a faster time.
I'm going to stress you again, but don't go ahead with DOWN quickly.
While you make the turn, if the pressure is raised by inclination by the edgging,
As the pressure goes up, you just feel like you're taking it slowly.
Go slowly~ slowly, do DOWN.
It's going to be a very important key point.
- Hand-Gliding Demonstration and precautions -
And as I said before,
from this episode on, you're going to put your hand on the slope.
As I told you last time,
it's such a bad habit to bend your upper body to touch your hand as soon as you begin a turn.
So you try not to put your hand on as much as you can,
but when the slope is too close to me,
to feel like getting ready to fall,
to feel like a light welcome to the approaching slope,
make it feel like you're picking up the slope.
For example, if you have a toe side turn,
you should never reach out like this to touch the slope first.
In the case of toe side turn, as I said before,
when you begin a turn, you push your pelvis in first.
Then you ride it while maintaining the angulation.
When the slope gets closer, you just take the slope lightly.
If you want to touch the slope first,
it's easy for your hips to protrude, so don't do that.
In the case of heel side turns, when you're trying to put your hand on the slope..
it's very important to fold your pelvis and maintain this angle of angulation,
As the pelvis folds out, the angulation angle is not made, making the edgging unstable.
So never touch your hands on purpose,
you just feel like you're going to meet you when you get close.
You can use your hands lightly.
And the last time, someone touched his/her hand,
touch on well, but there are people who put a lot of weight on his/her hand.
When the slope might be a little bad,
or when there is ice cubes, there are many people who can't make Carving turn at all if don't put your hands on.
You should be restrained the habit of the touching slope too strongly,
then, you try to put your hands as lightly as possible.
- demonstration on the slope -
I'm going to show you on the slope.
I'll show you how to Edge switching using UpDown, so to be exact, edge switching using up-unweight,
and how to touch your hands lightly.
I told you everything earlier many time, but what you need to remember now is.
Always be careful not to loosen your pelvis when performing UpDown.
And please always pay attention to angulation.
And when you do DOWN, don't do it too quickly.
As soon as you begin a turn, you can think of DOWN slowly to 3~4 o'clock.
Don't try to touch your hands when they're not made inclination.
If I don't have to touch it when I ride it, I won't touch it.
Just pick up when you feel like you have no choice but to come too close.
I'll tell you again that you shouldn't reach out to point out or do it again.
Let me show you a demonstration.
Actually, this deck is new and I'm not getting used to it.
So, I don't know if I can ride it well.
I'll try my best to show you in a good posture.
It's UP.
DOWN~~
UP~
Be careful not to loosen your pelvis in the process of UP!
The aim should never be to touch hands.
In particular, the pelvis is often closed when UP is performed after the toe turn, so be careful!!
I don't think I'm a good rider.
I'm doing UpDown like I just showed you.
Don't rush to do DOWN. Slowly do DOWN.
And don't take your hands to stretch like this on purposely.
Just in case, if you don't have enough inclinations,
so if it's hard to touch by reaching out, you don't put the hand to the slope.
When you increases your inclination as you increase your skills, and then you try to reach out.
I'll tell you again that you should never touch your hands.
Then I'll ride it a few more times.
I'll make a video of a good posture for you guys.
Now, come with me.
Let me show you again.
Go in toe side
DOWN~~
UP~
UP~DOWN~~
OK!